Progress check 6, exercise 6, page 69.
Kiểm tra tiến độ 6, bài tập 6, trang 69.
Listen and tick the box.
Nghe và đánh dấu vào ô.
There is one example.
Có một ví dụ.
What does Anna do on Saturdays?
Anna làm gì vào thứ Bảy?
Does Anna do her homework on Saturdays?
Anna có làm bài tập vào thứ Bảy không?
No, she doesn't.
Không.
Oh!
Ồ!
Does Anna watch TV then?
Vậy Anna có xem ti vi không?
No, on Saturdays she plays tennis with her friend, Sue.
Không, vào thứ Bảy bạn ấy chơi quần vợt với bạn Sue.
Can you see the tick?
Bạn có thấy dấu tích không?
Now you listen and tick the box.
Bây giờ bạn nghe và đánh dấu vào ô.
1.
What are David and Simon doing now?
David và Simon đang làm gì bây giờ?
Are David and Simon outside playing football?
David và Simon có đang chơi bóng đá ngoài trời không?
No, they aren't.
Không.
Are they having lunch?
Họ đang ăn trưa à?
No, they aren't.
Không.
They're drawing pictures.
Họ đang vẽ tranh.
2.
What does Jenny like?
Jenny thích gì?
Are you eating an apple, Jenny?
Bạn đang ăn táo à, Jenny?
No, I'm not.
Không.
I don't like apples.
Tôi không thích táo.
Are you eating a banana?
Bạn đang ăn chuối à?
No, I don't like bananas.
Không, tôi không thích chuối.
I'm eating an orange.
Tôi đang ăn cam.
3.
What is Becky wearing now?
Bây giờ Becky đang mặc gì?
Is Becky wearing a blue skirt today?
Hôm nay Becky có mặc váy xanh không?
No, she's wearing blue jeans.
Không, bạn ấy đang mặc quần bò xanh.
Is Becky wearing a red jacket?
Becky có mặc áo khoác đỏ không?
No, her jacket's green.
Không, áo khoác của bạn ấy màu xanh lá.
Now listen again.
Bây giờ hãy nghe lại.